Finding Aid for the University of Tennessee Theatre Collection, 1901- AR.0235
University of Tennessee Libraries, Special Collections
- Plays, 1941 February 18-2010 December 2-19; I; (Playbills, Photographs, Press Clippings, Production Materials, Posters, Stage Designs, and Scrapbooks)
  - Individual Plays, 1941 February 18-2010 December 19; A; (Playbills, Photographs, Press Clippings, Production Materials, Posters, Stage Designs, and Scrapbooks)
    - Pal Joey (Carousel Theatre), 1960 November 23-26, 28-December 3; (2 of 2); (Photographs) (Box 3, Folder 63)
    - The Heiress (Carousel Theatre), 1961 January 17-20, 23-25; (1 of 2); (Playbill) (Box 3, Folder 64)
    - The Heiress (Carousel Theatre), 1961 January 17-20, 23-25; (2 of 2); (Photographs) (Box 3, Folder 65)
    - Bad Seed (Carousel Theatre), 1961 January 25-28, 31-February 2; (Playbill) (Box 3, Folder 66)
    - Uncle Vanya: Scenes from Village Life (Carousel Theatre), 1961 February 8-11; (1 of 2); (Playbill) (Box 3, Folder 67)
    - Uncle Vanya: Scenes from Village Life (Carousel Theatre), 1961 February 8-11; (2 of 2); (Photographs) (Box 3, Folder 68)
    - The Reclining Figure (Carousel Theatre), 1961 March 15-18, 21-23; (1 of 2); (Playbill) (Box 3, Folder 69)
    - The Reclining Figure (Carousel Theatre), 1961 March 15-18, 21-23; (2 of 2); (Photographs) (Box 3, Folder 70)
    - Down in the Valley (Carousel Theatre), 1961 April 5-8; (Playbill) (Box 3, Folder 71)
    - The Voice of the Turtle (Carousel Theatre), 1961 April 19-22, 25-28; (1 of 2); (Playbill) (Box 3, Folder 72)
    - The Voice of the Turtle (Carousel Theatre), 1961 April 19-22, 25-28; (2 of 2); (Photographs) (Box 3, Folder 73)
    - The Fourposter (Carousel Theatre), 1961 June 27-July 1, 4-5; (1 of 2); (Playbill and Press Clippings) (Box 3, Folder 74)
    - The Fourposter (Carousel Theatre), 1961 June 27-July 1, 4-5; (2 of 2); (Photographs) (Box 3, Folder 75)
    - Anastasia (Carousel Theatre), 1961 July 11-15, 18-19; (1 of 2); (Playbill) (Box 3, Folder 76)
    - Anastasia (Carousel Theatre), 1961 July 11-15, 18-19; (2 of 2); (Photographs) (Box 3, Folder 77)
    - Androcles and the Lion (Carousel Theatre), 1961 July 25-29, August 1-2; (Playbill) (Box 3, Folder 78)
    - Twelfth Night, 1961 November 1-4; (Playbill) (Box 3, Folder 79)
    - Guys and Dolls (Carousel Theatre), 1961 November 22-25, 28-30; (1 of 2); (Playbill) (Box 3, Folder 80)
    - Guys and Dolls (Carousel Theatre), 1961 November 22-25, 28-30; (2 of 2); (Photographs) (Box 3, Folder 81)
    - Charley's Aunt, circa 1962; (Photographs) (Box 3, Folder 82)
    - The Importance of Being Earnest (Carousel Theatre), 1962 February 14-17; (Playbill) (Box 3, Folder 83)
    - The Chalk Circle (Carousel Theatre), 1962 April 4-7; (Playbill) (Box 3, Folder 84)
    - Odd Job; The Peckerwood; Nevsky Asunder (Carousel Theatre), 1962 April 24-26; (Playbill) (Box 3, Folder 85)
    - The Matchmaker, 1962 May; (Photographs) (Box 3, Folder 86)
    - Ten Little Indians (Carousel Theatre), 1962 July 24-August 1; (Playbill) (Box 3, Folder 87)
    - J.B., 1962 October 31-November 3; (Playbill) (Box 3, Folder 88)
    - Look Homeward, Angel (Carousel Theatre), 1963 January 16-19, 22-24; (1 of 2); (Playbill) (Box 3, Folder 89)
    - Look Homeward, Angel (Carousel Theatre), 1963 January 16-19, 22-24; (2 of 2); (Photographs) (Box 3, Folder 90)
    - The Zoo Story; The Bald Soprano (Carousel Theatre), 1963 February 13-16; (Playbill) (Box 3, Folder 91)
    - Bye Bye Birdie, 1963 March; (Photographs) (Box 3, Folder 92)
    - Mr. Roberts, 1963 April; (Photographs) (Box 3, Folder 93)
    - The Innocents (Carousel Theatre), 1963 April 3-6; (Playbill) (Box 3, Folder 94)
    - Critic's Choice (Carousel Theatre), 1963 July 9-13, 16-17; (Playbill) (Box 3, Folder 95)
    - Little Mary Sunshine, 1963 November; (Photographs) (Box 3, Folder 96)
    - The Imaginary Invalid (Carousel Theatre), 1963 November 6-9; (1 of 3); (Playbill) (Box 3, Folder 97)
    - The Imaginary Invalid (Carousel Theatre), 1963 November 6-9; (2 of 3); (Photographs) (Box 3, Folder 98)
    - The Imaginary Invalid (Carousel Theatre), 1963 November 6-9; (3 of 3); (Photographs) (Box 3, Folder 99)
    - Long Day's Journey Into Night (Carousel Theatre), 1964 January 22-25, 28-30; (1 of 2); (Playbill) (Box 3, Folder 100)
    - Long Day's Journey Into Night (Carousel Theatre), 1964 January 22-25, 28-30; (2 of 2); (Photographs) (Box 3, Folder 101)
    - Henry IV: Part I, 1964 February 12-15; (1 of 2); (Playbill) (Box 3, Folder 102)
    - Henry IV: Part I, 1964 February 12-15; (2 of 2); (Photographs) (Box 3, Folder 103)
    - Anniversary Waltz (Carousel Theatre), 1964 February 26-29, March 3-5; (1 of 2); (Playbill) (Box 3, Folder 104)
    - Anniversary Waltz (Carousel Theatre), 1964 February 26-29, March 3-5; (2 of 2); (Photographs) (Box 3, Folder 105)
    - Cat on a Hot Tin Roof (Carousel Theatre), 1964 April 15-18; (1 of 2); (Playbill) (Box 3, Folder 106)
    - Cat on a Hot Tin Roof (Carousel Theatre), 1964 April 15-18; (2 of 2); (Photographs) (Box 3, Folder 107)
    - The Little Foxes (Carousel Theatre), 1964 April 29-May 2, 5-7; (1 of 2); (Playbill) (Box 3, Folder 108)
    - The Little Foxes (Carousel Theatre), 1964 April 29-May 2, 5-7; (2 of 2); (Photographs) (Box 3, Folder 109)
    - Everybody Loves Opal (Carousel Theatre), 1964 June 17-20, 23-25; (1 of 2); (Playbill) (Box 4, Folder 1)
    - Everybody Loves Opal (Carousel Theatre), 1964 June 17-20, 23-25; (2 of 2); (Photographs) (Box 4, Folder 2)
    - State of the Union (Carousel Theatre), 1964 July 1-4, 7-8; (1 of 2); (Playbill) (Box 4, Folder 3)
    - State of the Union (Carousel Theatre), 1964 July 1-4, 7-8; (2 of 2); (Photographs) (Box 4, Folder 4)
    - All The King's Men (Carousel Theatre), 1964 July 29-August 1, 4-6; (1 of 2); (Playbill) (Box 4, Folder 5)
    - All The King's Men (Carousel Theatre), 1964 July 29-August 1, 4-6; (2 of 2); (Photographs) (Box 4, Folder 6)
    - Carousel (Carousel Theatre), 1964 August 12-15, 18-25; (1 of 3); (Playbill) (Box 4, Folder 7)
    - Carousel (Carousel Theatre), 1964 August 12-15, 18-25; (2 of 3); (Photographs) (Box 4, Folder 8)
    - Carousel (Carousel Theatre), 1964 August 12-15, 18-25; (3 of 3); (Photographs) (Box 4, Folder 9)
    - The Beaux' Stratagem (Carousel Theatre), 1964 November 13-17; (1 of 2); (Playbill) (Box 4, Folder 10)
    - The Beaux' Stratagem (Carousel Theatre), 1964 November 13-17; (2 of 2); (Photographs) (Box 4, Folder 11)
    - Tea and Sympathy (Carousel Theatre), 1964 November-December; (Photographs) (Box 4, Folder 12)
    - The Play's the Thing (Carousel Theatre), 1965 January 14-16, 19-22; (Playbill) (Box 4, Folder 13)
    - A Streetcar Named Desire (Carousel Theatre), 1965 April 1-3, 6-14; (1 of 2); (Playbill) (Box 4, Folder 14)
    - A Streetcar Named Desire (Carousel Theatre), 1965 April 1-3, 6-14; (2 of 2); (Photographs) (Box 4, Folder 15)
    - Kiss Me, Kate (Carousel Theatre), 1965 April 22-24, 27-30-May 1; (1 of 2); (Playbill) (Box 4, Folder 16)
    - Kiss Me, Kate (Carousel Theatre), 1965 April 22-24, 27-30-May 1; (2 of 2); (Photographs) (Box 4, Folder 17)
    - The Madwoman of Chaillot (Carousel Theatre), 1965 May 12-15; (1 of 2); (Playbill) (Box 4, Folder 18)
    - The Madwoman of Chaillot (Carousel Theatre), 1965 May 12-15; (2 of 2); (Photographs) (Box 4, Folder 19)
    - Golden Fleecing (Carousel Theatre), 1965 June 16-19, 22-24; (1 of 2); (Playbill) (Box 4, Folder 20)
    - Golden Fleecing (Carousel Theatre), 1965 June 16-19, 22-24; (2 of 2); (Photographs) (Box 4, Folder 21)
    - Sunday in New York (Carousel Theatre), 1965 June 30-July 3, 6-8; (1 of 2); (Playbill) (Box 4, Folder 22)
    - Sunday in New York (Carousel Theatre), 1965 June 30-July 3, 6-8; (2 of 2); (Photographs) (Box 4, Folder 23)
    - A Majority of One (Carousel Theatre), 1965 July 14-17, 20-22; (1 of 2); (Playbill) (Box 4, Folder 24)
    - A Majority of One (Carousel Theatre), 1965 July 14-17, 20-22; (2 of 2); (Photographs) (Box 4, Folder 25)
    - The Miracle Worker (Carousel Theatre), 1965 July 28-31, August 3-7; (1 of 2); (Playbill) (Box 4, Folder 26)
    - The Miracle Worker (Carousel Theatre), 1965 July 28-31, August 3-7; (2 of 2); (Photographs) (Box 4, Folder 27)
    - South Pacific (Carousel Theatre), 1965 August 11-14, 16-28; (1 of 2); (Playbill) (Box 4, Folder 28)
    - South Pacific (Carousel Theatre), 1965 August 11-14, 16-28; (2 of 2); (Photographs/Negatives) (Box 4, Folder 29)
    - Dark at the Top of the Stairs (Carousel Theatre), 1965 November; (Negatives) (Box 4, Folder 30)
    - Macbeth, 1965 November 5-15; (1 of 2); (Playbill) (Box 4, Folder 31)
    - Macbeth, 1965 November 5-15; (2 of 2); (Photographs) (Box 4, Folder 32)
    - Gypsy (Carousel Theatre), 1965 November 18-20, 23-26; (1 of 2); (Playbill) (Box 4, Folder 33)
    - Gypsy (Carousel Theatre), 1965 November 18-20, 23-26; (2 of 2); (Photographs) (Box 4, Folder 34)
    - Middle of the Night, circa 1966; (Photographs) (Box 4, Folder 35)
    - Five Finger Exercise (Carousel Theatre), 1966 January 13-15, 18-21; (1 of 2); (Playbill) (Box 4, Folder 36)
    - Five Finger Exercise (Carousel Theatre), 1966 January 13-15, 18-21; (2 of 2); (Photographs) (Box 4, Folder 37)
    - Thieves' Carnival (Carousel Theatre), 1966 February 18-19, 21-22; (1 of 2); (Playbill) (Box 4, Folder 38)
    - Thieves' Carnival (Carousel Theatre), 1966 February 18-19, 21-22; (2 of 2); (Photographs) (Box 4, Folder 39)
    - Auntie Mame (Carousel Theatre), 1966 March 24-26, 29-April 1; (1 of 2); (Playbill) (Box 4, Folder 40)
    - Auntie Mame (Carousel Theatre), 1966 March 24-26, 29-April 1; (2 of 2); (Photographs) (Box 4, Folder 41)
    - The Menaechmi (Carousel Theatre), 1966 April 13-16; (1 of 2); (Playbill) (Box 4, Folder 42)
    - The Menaechmi (Carousel Theatre), 1966 April 13-16; (2 of 2); (Photographs) (Box 4, Folder 43)
    - Kiss and Tell (Carousel Theatre), 1966 June 15-18, 21-23; (1 of 2); (Playbill) (Box 4, Folder 44)
    - Kiss and Tell (Carousel Theatre), 1966 June 15-18, 21-23; (2 of 2); (Photographs) (Box 4, Folder 45)
    - Once More, With Feeling (Carousel Theatre), 1966 June 29-July 2, 5-7; (1 of 2); (Playbill) (Box 4, Folder 46)
    - Once More, With Feeling (Carousel Theatre), 1966 June 29-July 2, 5-7; (2 of 2); (Photographs) (Box 4, Folder 47)
    - Present Laughter (Carousel Theatre), 1966 July 13-16, 19-21; (1 of 2); (Playbill) (Box 4, Folder 48)
    - Present Laughter (Carousel Theatre), 1966 July 13-16, 19-21; (2 of 2); (Photographs) (Box 4, Folder 49)
    - A Raisin in the Sun (Carousel Theatre), 1966 July 27-30, August 2-4; (1 of 2); (Playbill) (Box 4, Folder 50)
    - A Raisin in the Sun (Carousel Theatre), 1966 July 27-30, August 2-4; (2 of 2); (Photographs) (Box 4, Folder 51)
    - Enter Laughing (Carousel Theatre), 1966 October 20-22, 24-28; (1 of 2); (Playbill) (Box 4, Folder 52)
    - Enter Laughing (Carousel Theatre), 1966 October 20-22, 24-28; (2 of 2); (Photographs) (Box 4, Folder 53)
    - Becket (Carousel Theatre), 1966 November 2-5; (1 of 2); (Playbill) (Box 4, Folder 54)
    - Becket (Carousel Theatre), 1966 November 2-5; (2 of 2); (Photographs) (Box 4, Folder 55)
    - Oklahoma! (Carousel Theatre), 1966 November 17-19, 22-25; (1 of 2); (Playbill) (Box 4, Folder 56)
    - Oklahoma! (Carousel Theatre), 1966 November 17-19, 22-25; (2 of 2); (Photographs) (Box 4, Folder 57)
    - The Day's Mischief (Carousel Theatre), 1967 January 12-14, 17-20; (1 of 2); (Playbill and Press Clippings) (Box 4, Folder 58)
    - The Day's Mischief (Carousel Theatre), 1967 January 12-14, 17-20; (2 of 2); (Photographs) (Box 4, Folder 59)
    - Biedermann and the Firebug (Carousel Theatre), 1967 February 15-18; (1 of 2); (Playbill) (Box 4, Folder 60)
    - Biedermann and the Firebugs (Carousel Theatre), 1967 February 15-18; (2 of 2); (Photographs) (Box 4, Folder 61)
    - The Knack (Carousel Theatre), 1967 March 30-April 1, 4-7; (1 of 2); (Playbill) (Box 4, Folder 62)
    - The Knack (Carousel Theatre), 1967 March 30-April 1, 4-7; (2 of 2); (Photographs) (Box 4, Folder 63)
    - The Cocktail Party (Carousel Theatre), 1967 April 19-22; (1 of 2); (Playbill) (Box 4, Folder 64)
    - The Cocktail Party (Carousel Theatre), 1967 April 19-22; (2 of 2); (Photographs) (Box 4, Folder 65)
    - Someone Waiting (Carousel Theatre), 1967 May 4-6, 9-12; (1 of 2); (Playbill) (Box 4, Folder 66)
    - Someone Waiting (Carousel Theatre), 1967 May 4-6, 9-12; (2 of 2); (Photographs) (Box 4, Folder 67)
    - No Time for Sergeants (Carousel Theatre), 1967 June 15-17, 20-23; (1 of 2); (Playbill) (Box 4, Folder 68)
    - No Time for Sergeants (Carousel Theatre), 1967 June 15-17, 20-23; (2 of 2); (Photographs) (Box 4, Folder 69)
    - Look Back in Anger (Carousel Theatre), 1967 June 29-July 1, 4-7; (1 of 2); (Playbill) (Box 4, Folder 70)
    - Look Back in Anger (Carousel Theatre), 1967 June 29-July 1, 4-7; (2 of 2); (Photographs) (Box 4, Folder 71)
    - The Absence of a Cello (Carousel Theatre), 1967 July 13-15, 18-21; (1 of 2); (Playbill) (Box 4, Folder 72)
    - The Absence of a Cello (Carousel Theatre), 1967 July 13-15, 18-21; (2 of 2); (Photographs) (Box 4, Folder 73)
    - Glad Tidings (Carousel Theatre), 1967 July 27-29, August 1-3, 5; (1 of 2); (Playbill) (Box 4, Folder 74)
    - Glad Tidings (Carousel Theatre), 1967 July 27-29, August 1-3, 5; (2 of 2); (Photographs) (Box 4, Folder 75)
    - How to Succeed in Business Without Really Trying (Carousel Theatre), 1967 August 10-12, 15-18; (1 of 2); (Playbill) (Box 4, Folder 76)
    - How to Succeed in Business Without Really Trying (Carousel Theatre), 1967 August 10-12, 15-18; (2 of 2); (Photographs) (Box 4, Folder 77)
    - Come Back, Little Sheba (Carousel Theatre), 1967 October 12-14, 17-20; (1 of 2); (Playbill) (Box 4, Folder 78)
    - Come Back, Little Sheba (Carousel Theatre), 1967 October 12-14, 17-20; (2 of 2); (Photographs) (Box 4, Folder 79)
    - Love for Love, 1967 October 25-28; (Playbill) (Box 4, Folder 80)
    - West Side Story (Carousel Theatre), 1967 November 16-18, 21-24; (1 of 2); (Playbill) (Box 4, Folder 81)
    - West Side Story (Carousel Theatre), 1967 November 16-18, 21-24; (2 of 2); (Photographs) (Box 4, Folder 82)
    - Alice in Wonderland, circa 1968; (Photographs) (Box 4, Folder 83)
    - The Caretaker (Carousel Theatre), 1968 February 21-24; (1 of 2); (Playbill) (Box 4, Folder 84)
    - The Caretaker (Carousel Theatre), 1968 February 21-24; (2 of 2); (Photographs) (Box 4, Folder 85)
    - Spoon River Anthology, 1968 March 5-6; (Playbill) (Box 4, Folder 86)
    - The Waltz of the Toreadors (Carousel Theatre), 1968 March 28-30, April 2-5; (Photographs) (Box 4, Folder 87)
    - The Insect Comedy (Carousel Theatre), 1968 April 17-20; (Playbill) (Box 4, Folder 88)
    - Who's Afraid of Virginia Woolf? (Carousel Theatre), 1968 May 2-4, 7-10; (1 of 2); (Playbill) (Box 4, Folder 89)
    - Who's Afraid of Virginia Woolf? (Carousel Theatre), 1968 May 2-4, 7-10; (2 of 2); (Photographs) (Box 4, Folder 90)
    - The Typists and the Tiger (Carousel Theatre), 1968 June 20-22, 25-28; (1 of 2); (Playbill) (Box 4, Folder 91)
    - The Typists and the Tiger (Carousel Theatre), 1968 June 20-22, 25-28; (2 of 2); (Photographs) (Box 4, Folder 92)
    - The Children's Hour (Carousel Theatre), 1968 July 4-6, 9-12; (Photographs) (Box 4, Folder 93)
    - Harold (Carousel Theatre), 1968 July 18-20, 23-26; (1 of 2); (Playbill) (Box 5, Folder 1)
    - Harold (Carousel Theatre), 1968 July 18-20, 23-26; (2 of 2); (Photographs) (Box 5, Folder 2)
    - The Odd Couple (Carousel Theatre), 1968 August 1-3, 6-9; (1 of 2); (Playbill) (Box 5, Folder 3)
    - The Odd Couple (Carousel Theatre), 1968 August 1-3, 6-9; (2 of 2); (Photographs) (Box 5, Folder 4)
    - A Funny Thing Happened on the Way to the Forum (Carousel Theatre), 1968 August 15-17, 20-23; (1 of 2); (Playbill) (Box 5, Folder 5)
    - A Funny Thing Happened on the Way to the Forum (Carousel Theatre), 1968 August 15-17, 20-23; (2 of 2); (Photographs) (Box 5, Folder 6)
    - The Subject Was Roses (Carousel Theatre), 1968 October 17-19, 21-25; (1 of 2); (Playbill) (Box 5, Folder 7)
    - The Subject Was Roses (Carousel Theatre), 1968 October 17-19, 21-25; (2 of 2); (Photographs) (Box 5, Folder 8)
    - Luther (Carousel Theatre), 1968 October 30-November 2; (1 of 2); (Playbill and Press Clippings) (Box 5, Folder 9)
    - Luther (Carousel Theatre), 1968 October 30-November 2; (2 of 2); (Photographs) (Box 5, Folder 10)
    - Guys and Dolls (Carousel Theatre), 1968 November 14-16, 19-22; (1 of 3); (Playbill) (Box 5, Folder 11)
    - Guys and Dolls (Carousel Theatre), 1968 November 14-16, 19-22; (2 of 3); (Photographs) (Box 5, Folder 12)
    - Guys and Dolls (Carousel Theatre), 1968 November 14-16, 19-22; (3 of 3); (Photographs) (Box 5, Folder 13)
    - Period of Adjustment or High Point is Built on a Cavern (Carousel Theatre), 1969 January 30-February 1, 4-7; (1 of 2); (Playbills) (Box 5, Folder 14)
    - Period of Adjustment or High Point is Built on a Cavern (Carousel Theatre), 1969 January 30-February 1, 4-7; (2 of 2); (Photographs) (Box 5, Folder 15)
    - The Rimers of Eldritch (Carousel Theatre), 1969 February 19-22; (1 of 2); (Playbills) (Box 5, Folder 16)
    - The Rimers of Eldritch (Carousel Theatre), 1969 February 19-22; (2 of 2); (Photographs) (Box 5, Folder 17)
    - Philadelphia, Here I Come (Carousel Theatre), 1969 April 3-5, 8-11; (1 of 3); (Playbills) (Box 5, Folder 18)
    - Philadelphia, Here I Come (Carousel Theatre), 1969 April 3-5, 8-11; (2 of 3); (Photographs) (Box 5, Folder 19)
    - Philadelphia, Here I Come (Carousel Theatre), 1969 April 3-5, 8-11; (3 of 3); (Photographs) (Box 5, Folder 20)
    - The Threepenny Opera (Carousel Theatre), 1969 April 16-19; (1 of 3); (Playbills) (Box 5, Folder 21)
    - The Threepenny Opera (Carousel Theatre), 1969 April 16-19; (2 of 3); (Photographs) (Box 5, Folder 22)
    - The Threepenny Opera (Carousel Theatre), 1969 April 16-19; (3 of 3); (Photographs) (Box 5, Folder 23)
    - The Owl and the Pussycat (Carousel Theatre), 1969 May 1-3, 6-9; (1 of 2); (Playbills) (Box 5, Folder 24)
    - The Owl and the Pussycat (Carousel Theatre), 1969 May 1-3, 6-9; (2 of 2); (Photographs) (Box 5, Folder 25)
    - My Three Angels (Carousel Theatre), 1969 June 19-21, 24-27; (1 of 2); (Playbills) (Box 5, Folder 26)
    - My Three Angels (Carousel Theatre), 1969 June 19-21, 24-27; (2 of 2); (Photographs) (Box 5, Folder 27)
    - The Dock Brief; Black Comedy (Carousel Theatre), 1969 July 3-5, 8-11; (1 of 3); (Playbills) (Box 5, Folder 28)
    - The Dock Brief; Black Comedy (Carousel Theatre), 1969 July 3-5, 8-11; (2 of 3); (Photographs) (Box 5, Folder 29)
    - The Dock Brief; Black Comedy (Carousel Theatre), 1969 July 3-5, 8-11; (3 of 3); (Photographs) (Box 5, Folder 30)
    - Barefoot in the Park (Carousel Theatre), 1969 July 17-19, 22-25; (1 of 2); (Playbills) (Box 5, Folder 31)
    - Barefoot in the Park (Carousel Theatre), 1969 July 17-19, 22-25; (2 of 2); (Photographs) (Box 5, Folder 32)
    - Blue Denim (Carousel Theatre), 1969 July 31-August 2, 5-8; (1 of 2); (Playbills) (Box 5, Folder 33)
    - Blue Denim (Carousel Theatre), 1969 July 31-August 2, 5-8; (2 of 2); (Photographs) (Box 5, Folder 34)
    - Once Upon a Mattress (Carousel Theatre), 1969 August 14-16, 19-22; (1 of 2); (Press Clipping) (Box 5, Folder 35)
    - Once Upon a Mattress (Carousel Theatre), 1969 August 14-16, 19-22; (2 of 2); (Photographs) (Box 5, Folder 36)
    - Orpheus Descending (Carousel Theatre), 1969 October 23-25, 27-29, 31; (1 of 2); (Playbills) (Box 5, Folder 37)
    - Orpheus Descending (Carousel Theatre), 1969 October 23-25, 27-29, 31; (2 of 2); (Photographs) (Box 5, Folder 38)
    - Arlecchino: Servant of Two Masters (Carousel Theatre), 1969 November 5-8; (1 of 2); (Playbills) (Box 5, Folder 39)
    - Arlecchino: Servant of Two Masters (Carousel Theatre), 1969 November 5-8; (2 of 2); (Photographs) (Box 5, Folder 40)
    - The Fantasticks (Carousel Theatre), 1969 November 20-22, 24-26, 28; (1 of 2); (Playbills) (Box 5, Folder 41)
    - The Fantasticks (Carousel Theatre), 1969 November 20-22, 24-26, 28; (2 of 2); (Photographs) (Box 5, Folder 42)
    - The Lion in Winter (Carousel Theatre), 1970 January 29-31, February 2-4, 6; (1 of 2); (Playbill - Cover Only) (Box 5, Folder 43)
    - The Lion in Winter (Carousel Theatre), 1970 January 29-31, February 2-4, 6; (2 of 2); (Photographs) (Box 5, Folder 44)
    - The Grass Harp (Carousel Theatre), 1970 February 18-21; (1 of 2); (Playbills) (Box 5, Folder 45)
    - The Grass Harp (Carousel Theatre), 1970 February 18-21; (2 of 2); (Photographs) (Box 5, Folder 46)
    - Irma La Douce (Carousel Theatre), 1970 April 2-4, 6-10; (1 of 2); (Playbill and Press Clippings) (Box 5, Folder 47)
    - Irma La Douce (Carousel Theatre), 1970 April 2-4, 6-10; (2 of 2); (Photographs) (Box 5, Folder 48)
    - Don't Drink the Water (Carousel Theatre), 1970 April 30-May 2, 4-6, 8; (Playbills) (Box 5, Folder 49)
    - Hail Scrawdyle! (Carousel Theatre), 1970 May 18-21; (1 of 2); (Playbills) (Box 5, Folder 50)
    - Hail Scrawdyle! (Carousel Theatre), 1970 May 18-21; (2 of 2); (Photographs) (Box 5, Folder 51)
    - You Know I Can't Hear You When the Water's Running (Carousel Theatre), 1970 June 18-20, 22-24, 26; (1 of 2); (Playbill and Press Clippings) (Box 5, Folder 52)
    - You Know I Can't Hear You When the Water's Running (Carousel Theatre), 1970 June 18-20, 22-24, 26; (2 of 2); (Photographs) (Box 5, Folder 53)
    - Dracula (Carousel Theatre), 1970 June 2-4, 6-8, 10; (Photographs) (Box 5, Folder 54)
    - The Star-Spangled Girl (Carousel Theatre), 1970 July 16-18, 20-22, 24; (1 of 2); (Press Clippings) (Box 5, Folder 55)
    - The Star-Spangled Girl (Carousel Theatre), 1970 July 16-18, 20-22, 24; (2 of 2); (Photographs) (Box 5, Folder 56)
    - We Bombed in New Haven (Carousel Theatre), 1970 July 30-August 1, 3-5, 7; (1 of 2); (Playbill and Press Clippings) (Box 5, Folder 57)
    - We Bombed in New Haven (Carousel Theatre), 1970 July 30-August 1, 3-5, 7; (2 of 2); (Photographs) (Box 5, Folder 58)
    - Damn Yankees (Carousel Theatre), 1970 August 13-15, 17-19, 21; (1 of 2); (Press Clippings) (Box 5, Folder 59)
    - Damn Yankees (Carousel Theatre), 1970 August 13-15, 17-19, 21; (2 of 2); (Photographs) (Box 5, Folder 60)
    - The Boys in the Band (Carousel Theatre), 1970 October 21-24, 26-28; (1 of 2); (Playbill and Press Clippings) (Box 5, Folder 61)
    - The Boys in the Band (Carousel Theatre), 1970 October 21-24, 26-28; (2 of 2); (Photographs) (Box 5, Folder 62)
    - A Delicate Balance (Carousel Theatre), 1970 November 5-7, 9-12; (1 of 2); (Playbills) (Box 5, Folder 63)
    - A Delicate Balance (Carousel Theatre), 1970 November 5-7, 9-12; (2 of 2); (Photographs) (Box 5, Folder 64)
    - Look Homeward, Angel (Clarence Brown Theatre), 1970 November 14, 16-21; (1 of 2); (Playbills and Press Clippings) (Box 5, Folder 65)
    - Look Homeward, Angel (Clarence Brown Theatre), 1970 November 14, 16-21; (2 of 2); (Photographs) (Box 5, Folder 66)
    - Dracula (Carousel Theatre), circa 1971; (Negatives) (Box 5, Folder 67)
    - Conerico Was Here to Stay; Big Sur, 1971 January-February; (Playbills) (Box 5, Folder 68)
    - The Crucible (Carousel Theatre), 1971 February 18, 20, 22-24, 26; (1 of 2); (Playbill and Press Clippings) (Box 5, Folder 69)
    - The Crucible (Carousel Theatre), 1971 February 18, 20, 22-24, 26; (2 of 2); (Photographs) (Box 5, Folder 70)
    - Man of La Mancha (Clarence Brown Theatre), 1971 March 26-27, 29-31, April 2; (1 of 2); (Playbills) (Box 5, Folder 71)
    - Man of La Mancha (Clarence Brown Theatre), 1971 March 26-27, 29-31, April 2; (2 of 2); (Photographs) (Box 5, Folder 72)
    - Viet Rock (Carousel Theatre), 1971 April 9-10, 12-14, 16-17; (1 of 2); (Press Clippings) (Box 5, Folder 73)
    - Viet Rock (Carousel Theatre), 1971 April 9-10, 12-14, 16-17; (2 of 2); (Photographs) (Box 5, Folder 74)